亲爱的 你会买一款叫做...
Honey, would you buy a closet called --
我在等通知 看我明天能不能去
I am waiting to see if I get to go tomorrow.
陪审员义务 其实你可以直接把电话扔在一边
Jury duty. You know, you can just throw that away.
那样他们就无法通知你你被选中了
There's no way they can ever tell you got it.
杰 你是不合格的美国人
Jay, you're a bad American.
能在陪审团发挥作用是一种荣耀
It is a privilege to serve on a jury.
我有史以来第一次可以参与了
For the first time, I get to be part of it.
等你吃着从自动售货机买来的
Talk to me when you're eating
金枪鱼三明治再跟我说这话吧
a tuna sandwich out of a machine.
总之 那款是浮雕橡木材质 我想取名为...
Anyway, it's a distressed-oak model that I like to call --
等等 等等 等着
Wait, wait! Wait!
我被选中了
I'm in!
明早8点 C区停车楼
8:00 a.m. tomorrow. Parking structure "C"!
你对停车楼感到很激动吗
You're excited about a parking structure?
连A区或B区都不是
It's not even "A" or "B."
你得接替我去乔的学校做伴护
You're gonna have to take my place working at Joe's school.
我做不到啊 我有工作的
I can't do that. I have a job.
让克莱尔帮你顶着
Have Claire cover for you.
她知道怎么吼员工 看报纸
She knows how to yell at people and read the newspaper.
那学校是有什么毛病啊
What the hell's wrong with that school?
我们付他们钱 不就是为了不用亲自照顾孩子吗
Aren't we paying them so we don't have to take care of our kid?
学习谷仓不是这种制度
That's not the way it works at the learning barn.
他们希望家长也能参与进来
You know that they want the parents to be involved
那样就能增进跟孩子的感情
so that they can bond with the kids.
这年头的学校是发什么神经啊
What's wrong with schools today?
我现在很成功
I'm successful,
我当年的老师不过就是个长胡子的修女
and I had a nun with a mustache.
你最好习惯到那里去
Well, you better get used to going there,
因为如果我参审[卷入]的是件谋杀案
Because if I get put into a murder trial,
我可能得去[进牢]好几周呢
I could be gone for weeks.
或许我该告诉他们
Maybe I should tell them
我有在枪决队的经验
that I have experience on a firing squad.
你为什么要说这种疯话啊
Why do you say crazy stuff like that?
那不是真的 对吧
Now, that isn't true, is it?
等等
Wait a second.
那款新衣柜 我刚刚说叫什么来着
That new closet, what did I say it was called?
你没说出来
You never said.
该死的
Damn it!
我洗澡时非得要放支油性铅笔在旁边
That's why I need a grease pencil in the shower.
我也说不清 海莉
Oh, I don't know, Haley.
他很帅 很聪明 也很幽默
I mean, he is really cute and really smart and really funny,
但是 他总是穿木底鞋
But, oh, he's always wearing clogs.
不 不行
No, no.
如果他不是个大厨 护士或是郁金香销售员
If he is not a chef, a nurse, or a tulip salesman,
你得赶紧躲开
you need to run.
如果你妈对穿木底鞋的男人也是这种态度
If your mother had that attitude about a man in clogs,
你们俩就不会有我这亲爹了
you two wouldn't have a dad.
好的 谢谢 老爸 我不会让你失望的
Okay, thanks, Dad. I won't let you down.
再见
Bye.
猜猜怎么着 各位
Guess what, guys.
明天我会暂时充当公司的老大
I am going to be the big boss at work tomorrow,
巧的是 明天恰好是"带女儿去公司日"
And coincidentally, it's take your daughter to work day.
我可以跟你一起去公司 老妈
I'll go to work with you, Mom.
别想逃避社区服务了
Stop trying to get out of community service.
你需要攒够足够时间才能毕业
You need those hours to graduate.
再说你又不是女儿身
And you're not a daughter.
老妈 老爸 坐下
Mom, Dad, sit down.
我有件事要告诉你们
There's something I need to talk to you about.
你必须去
You're going.
姑娘们 你们意下如何
So, girls, what do you say?
我们又不是八岁小孩了 我还是有工作的人
You know we're not 8, and I have a job.
你上周因为长了青春痘 就请了两次病假
You called in sick twice last week because you had a zit.
我是在时尚行业工作的 他们叫我别去的
I work in fashion. They told me not to come in.
艾丽克斯 宝贝
Alex, honey,
你明天最后一节课是上午10点
your last class tomorrow is at 10:00 a.m.,
-不 不 不 -如果你早点出发
- No, no, no, no! -So, if you hit the road
海莉 快把电脑合上
Haley, quick, close the laptop!
在此之前 我一直是个全职妈妈
Until now, I was always a full-time mom,
所以女儿们一直没能看到我的另一面
So the girls never had a chance to see the other side of me --
就是 强势的女高层
You know, powerful woman in charge.
是啊 我们从"没机会"看到你强势的一面呢
Yeah, 'cause we never get to see your tough side.
快点 大爸 你工作要迟到了
Come on, Daddy, we're gonna be late for your work.
我知道 我也很激动
I know. I'm excited, too.
好吧 我错了
Okay, I was wrong.
在外吹口哨并没有好一些
The whistles aren't better outside.
你确定你一个人可以把这些杂货都弄回家吗
Are you sure you can get all these groceries home by yourself?
我不知道 我有点害怕
I don't know. I'm kind of scared.
我以前从未开车载过杂货回家呢
I've never driven groceries home before.
你们好啊
Hey, you guys.
雷 雷蒙德
Ray-- Raymond?
你好啊 好久不见
Hi. Oh, it's been so long.
是啊 自从那事后 就没见过你们了
Yeah. Haven't seen you since, you know.
是啊
Yeah.
雷蒙德和杰马库斯三个月前分手了
Raymond and J'marcus broke up three months ago,
他们在一起的时间和我们差不多
And they'd been together almost as long as we have.
杰马库斯继续和原来的朋友交往着
J'marcus got all the friends,
而雷蒙德沦落到穿着睡衣去购物
And Raymond got all the confidence to go shopping in his pajamas.
你们要办派对吗
You guys having a party?
-不 什么派对 -不 不是办派对
- No, no. Party? - No, not a party.
橄榄杂烩 方巾 三式饼干
Olive medley, square napkins, cracker trio.
这些东西只是为了...
well, these things are just more for a --
你觉得该怎么说好呢
What would you say?
小聚吗
Kind of like a get-together?
小聚 小聚 是临时决定的
Get-together, get-together. It's a last-minute thing.
没什么的
It's no big deal.
听上去很有趣
Sounds fun.
-不 很无趣的 -是啊 就饼干嘛
- No, it's not gonna be fun. - No. It's crackers.
到时候会下雨的
It's supposed to rain.
那再见了
I'll see you guys.
-好 -回见了 雷蒙德
- Yes. - You, too, Raymond.
-再见 -照顾好自己
- Bye-bye. - Take care of yourself.
刚刚好险啊
That was close.
我以为我们不得不邀请他了呢
I thought we were gonna have to invite him.
雷蒙德 你今晚也该来的
Raymond, you should come tonight.
真的吗
Really?
没有雷蒙德 算什么小聚啊
It wouldn't be a get-together without Raymond.
-对吧 小卡 -绝对的
- Right, Cam? - Absolutely.
是啊 但是你知道吗 那个...
Yeah. Oh, you know what? But...
我得提醒你一下 杰马库斯也会去的
I should tell you, J'marcus is gonna be there.
所以如果你觉得那样很尴尬
So, if that's gonna be uncomfortable,
我们完全理解的
we totally understand.
不 没事 我会去的
No, it's fine. I'll be there.
能再次见到杰马库斯也挺好的
It'll be nice to see J'marcus again.
或许他会带一个裸上身的腹肌婊过去
Maybe he'll bring one of those shirtless ab sluts
我在他脸书上都看到了
I've seen on his facebook page.
-回见 -好的 回见
- I'll see you guys. - Yeah. Yeah, see ya.
好的 我很期待
Okay. Look forward to it.
-回见 -好的
- you, too. - Yeah.
我能怎么做啊
What was I supposed to do?
他那么伤心 可悲 心碎
I mean, he was all sad and pathetic and broken.
是啊 任何派对都需要这样一个人呢
Well, yes, the perfect addition to any party.
他们一定会撕逼撕得天昏地暗
They are gonna be at each other's throats
毁了整个晚上 走吧 莉莉
and ruin the whole night. Come on, Lily.
都怪你 这次的派对
Thanks to you, we are throwing
肯定是这个社交季最反社会的
the antisocial event of the season.
-小卡 -不 先不说了 我要迟到了
- Cam. - No, I'm late and I'd like to leave on that.
你好 我来了
Hi. I'm -- I'm here.
真是惊喜啊
Well, this is a special treat.
我竟然看到了一位第一次出现的志愿者
I spy with my little eye a first-time volunteer!
歌洛莉亚要去做陪审团
Gloria had jury duty,
所以我能假装种族歧视
so no chance I could get out of this
不来做志愿者吗
by pretending to be racist?
总之 你要我做什么
Anyway, uh... what do you need?
你可以准备颜料 做甘蓝冰沙
You can set up the paints, make the kale smoothies,
然后把兔笼擦干净
and wipe down the rabbit hutch.
知道了 玛格丽特
On it. Margaret?
画笔 冰沙 笼子
Paint, smoothies, hutch.
知道了
Got it.
不好意思 这位是谁
Excuse me. Who's this?
她是玛格丽特 我的助理
That's Margaret, my assistant.
我没法有小孩
I couldn't have children.
父母志愿者不应该是这样的
This is not how it works with parent volunteers.
你对于"志愿者"的态度已经很随便了
You're already playing fast and loose
所以你想怎么样
with that term "volunteer," so...what do you say?
虽然我们不喜欢用"不"这个字
As much as we don't like to use the word "No" --
而且 如果这些小崽子们敢乱来
And, by the way, if any of these little tykes start acting up,
她可是有一百种方法让他们安生下来
she's not afraid to get out the wooden spoon.
杰 我知道你怕怕
Jay, I know it's a little scary,
但你必须得让她走
but you're going to have to let her go.
我不想让她走
I don't want her to go.
玛格丽特 走吧 我来吸引他的注意力
Margaret, just go. I'll distract him.
回来
Come back.
玛格丽特 不要回头
Margaret, don't turn around.
好吧 各位
Okay, men.
都过来
Gather 'round.
教学时间
Teachable moment.
不要把社区服务当成一种要求
Don't think of community service as a requirement.
把清洁这座公园当成一个机会
Think of cleaning up this park as an opportunity.
得肝炎的机会吗
To get hepatitis?
让世界更美好的机会
To make the world a better place.
所以我才来的
That's why I'm here.
我已经做完我该做的时间了
I already did my required hours.
用这种方式表明你还是处男挺酷炫的
That's a fancy way of saying you're a virgin.
随便你们开玩笑 但这种经历在申请纽约大学
Joke all you want, but this looks good on an application to NYU
加州大学洛杉矶分校或肯德基时会很有用
or UCLA or KFC.
好吧 别说废话了 开始捡垃圾吧
Okay, stop trash-talking and start trash picking...up.
我一会儿就来
I-I'll get that.
是你啊
There he is.
你好啊
You.
有多久没见了 房地产先生
How long's it been, Mr. Real estate?
你说呢 这位先生
Well, you tell me, Mr. You.
我通常很擅长记名字和脸
I'm usually really good with names and faces,
可我不记得这个人是谁了
but I could not remember who this guy was.
幸好 我知道一个好问题
Fortunately, I found that one perfectly worded question
能让你知道想要的所有信息
can get you all the information you need.
一切都好吗
How's things?
很好
Good.
你美丽的妻子近来如何
How's the beautiful wife?
克莱尔过得很好
Claire's great. Yeah.
多谢你的问候
Thank you so much for asking.
那 那你怎么样啊
How's... how's your situation?
你知道的 老样子
You know, same old, same old.
实际上 这个时候遇到你我很高兴
Actually, I'm glad I'm running into you like this.
我的车刚被拖走了
My car just got towed,
我的钱包和手机都在里面
and my wallet and cellphone were in there.
你能借我点钱打的吗
Could you possibly lend me some money for cab fare or...
好
Yes.
-多谢 -没事
- Thanks. - Of course.
给你四十块外加一点零钱
How's, uh, $40 with a little extra
以防万一 如何
in case you run into trouble?
我希望你能来得及赶回家
I want to make sure you get back to your house in, uh --
希望赶得上吃晚饭
Time for dinner, I hope.
多谢了 哥们儿 你最棒了
Thanks, man. You're the best.
老爸
Hey, Dad.
天哪
Oh, my god.
我上次见你的时候 你才这么点大
Last time I saw you, you were so small.
我得走了 多谢 朋友
I better run. Thanks, pal.
是啊 伙计 见到你真好
All right, buddy. Good to see you.
老爸
Dad.
那个人刚把你骗了
That guy just scammed you.
不 他没有
No, he didn't.
这是经典的诈骗方式
It's a classic scam.
假装认识对方然后借钱
You pretend you know someone and then borrow money.
好吧
Okay.
大家围过来 教学时刻
Men, gather 'round. Teachable mome-- hey.
围成一个圈 过来的意思是围成圈
Just -- a circle. Gather means a circle.
你们刚刚看到了什么
What did you just see?
小松鼠在吃创可贴
A squirrel eating a band-aid.
不 你们看到了一个人对朋友伸出援手
No. You saw a man helping out a friend in need.
如果他是你朋友 那他叫什么
If he was your friend, what's his name?
只是突然想不起来了
That slipped my mind.
你认得他的样子吗
Did you recognize him at all?
先生们 不要像卢克把别人都看扁
Gentlemen, don't be cynics like Luke.
不要让你们的紧身牛仔裤限制了良心供血
Don't let your skinny jeans cut off the blood to your hearts.
我支持你 菲尔
I'm with you, Phil.
我相信人性本善
I choose to believe in the goodness of men.
你鞋子上沾着一个套套
You have a condom stuck to your shoe.
被告对14号陪审员所言无异议
Defense also has no objection to juror 14.
继续 15号陪审员
Moving on, juror 15.
来吧 随便问 我是美国人
Here. Ask me anything. I am an American.
好吧
All right.
如果有人请了律师
When someone hires a lawyer,
你觉得他们更可能有罪吗
do you think they're more likely to be guilty?
不
No.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果他们像他那样玩头发
When they play with their hair like he is,
那我就知道他们有罪了
that's when I know that they're guilty.
法官大人 我们请求免职15号陪审员
Your honor, we request dismissal of juror 15.
为什么 我很擅长解读人性
Why? I'm very good at reading people.
他有罪
He is guilty.
另外 他后面那个男人也是
And, by the way, so is the guy that is behind him.
他都没有受审
He's not even on trial.
那他应该受审
Well, then he should be.
我不知道你做了什么 但你肯定做了
I don't know what you did, but you did it!
法官大人
Your honor.
他溜了
He's getting away.
15号陪审员 你被免职了
Juror 15, you are dismissed.
不 求你了 法官阁下
Ay! No, please, your excellency.
我只是想履行公民义务
I just want to do my part as a citizen.
女士 请不要犯傻了 出去
Lady, you can stop acting crazy. You got out.
姑娘们 这边 请进
Ladies, right this way. Come on in.
你在外公的办公室里工作吗
Oh, you're in grandpa's office?
当然了
Yeah. Of course I am.
这没什么 我一直在这里
It's no big deal. I'm in here all the time.
基本上 每天的这个时间都在
I mean, practically every day at this...this point.
这个
This is...
这椅子平常不是这样的
It's not usually such a...thing.
好了 你们坐吧
There we go. Have a seat.
身上有纹身的那个人还在装卸货车间工作吗
Does that guy with the tattoos still work on the loading docks?
我十五岁的时候 我第一次被人嘘就是他
When I was 15, he gave me my first catcall.
那天应该是他最后一天上班
Pretty sure that was his last day.
杰呢
where's Jay?
他不在 今天我代班
He's not here, but I'm filling in.
有事吗
What can I do you for?
我明天再来
I'll ask him tomorrow.
你确定
Are you sure?
男人总是被强势的女人吓到
Men are often intimidated by a strong, powerful woman.
杰在吗
Jay around?
他不在
No, he's not.
糟了
Oh, damn it.
可是掌控大局的人还在
Captain's chair is not empty.
让我来帮你吧
I'm here. Let me help you.
-你确定 -确定
- Seriously? - Seriously, huh?
我们要送100个装了镜子的门
Okay. Well, we need to take a delivery of 100 mirrored doors,
可是一号二号仓库都满了
but warehouse one and two are both full.
我知道怎么办 我能行
Okay, I know what to do. I've got this. Uh...
如果我们把抽屉全部塞到四号装卸车间
What if we move the drawers into that busted semi
那个烂半挂车里呢
in loading dock four?
-那样可以 因为 -二号仓库就空出来了
- And that works because-- - That frees up warehouse two.
最坏无非我们要晚一天才送到
Worst-case scenario, we're a day late on delivery.
客户会生气了
But they'll be mad at us.
如果我们在运费上折中一下呢
We'll give them a break off shipping?
我不知道 也许
I don't know. Maybe like --
打九折
10%! Ha.
成功了
We did it. Yeah!
干得漂亮 大伙
Good job, team.
我在这里的工作就是
You see, what I did there
构建一个解决问题的整体框架
is I created a framework for problem solving,
但是我不会直接告诉他们答案
and I didn't spoon-feed them the answers.
这就是绝妙的管理技能
It's just good management.
-是啊 -太绝妙了
- Yeah. - That's exactly what it looked like.
杰 我需要你帮忙决定 不好
Hey, Jay, I need a decision on that -- oh, boy.
回来 多姆
Get back here, Dom.
要决定什么
What needs to be decided?
赫姆要退休了 我们要为他举办派对
Well, we're throwing that party later for Herm's retirement,
杰特别擅长
and Jay's just sort of the master
给别人选蛋糕
when it comes to picking out cakes.
我来吧 我来选蛋糕
Oh, I'm here. I can pick out a cake.
冰淇淋蛋糕
Ice cream cake.
我说不好
I don't know about that.
就是个蛋糕而已 就它了
It's a cake. It'll be fine.
-有什么方式能让我联系 -赶紧去买吧
- Okay, is there a number where I could reach... - Just get it.
到杰吗
Jay?
不管事大事小
No matter how big or small the issue,
下属希望他们的领导有决断力
people want their leaders to be decisive.
-绝对的 -当然
- Oh, definitely. - Of course.
-什么口味 -薄荷味
- What flavor? - Mint chip.
-还是算了 -我说了薄荷味
- I'll come back. - I said mint chip!
乔 你想...
Hey, Joe! You want to...
我看起来像《灵异第六感》里的布鲁斯·威利斯
I'm like Bruce Willis in "The Sixth Sense."
杰 你能把手工桌
Jay, will you please put the craft table
放到麻毯上吗
over on the hemp rug?
不
No.
你说不爱用"不"这个字 可我咋老听见你用
For a word you don't use, I'm sure hearing it a lot.
那个才是手工桌
That's the craft table.
你现在拿的是情感桌
You're holding the feelings table,
我们只在谈论各自感受的时候才用
where we talk about how we feel.
桌子先生 我真想把你摔在她身上
Hey, Mr.Table, I feel like breaking you over a hippie.
你可是律师
Well, you're the lawyer.
我什么时候才能再去陪审团啊
When can I go to jury duty again?
我也不知道
you know, I have no idea.
你算是第一个问这种问题的人
You're literally the first person who has ever asked that.
我太难过了
I am so frustrated.
这让我想起小时候还在村子里
This reminds me when I was a little girl in my village
当时我们一点权力[电力]都没有
and we had no power.
你是说村里的电视
Oh, this is the story about the TV set
全靠驴子发电那个故事吗
powered by the donkey, right?
不是 我说的是政治权力
No, political power.
我们没有任何发言权
We had no say in anything.
可现在我是美国人了
But now I am an American,
我以为事情会不一样
so I thought things were going to be different.
我想要听证词 看证据
I wanted to listen to testimony, look at the evidence,
看到有人带着新的信息闯进来
have somebody burst in with new information.
米奇尔 猜猜发生了什么
Mitchell, guess what just happened.
你早回家了
You're home early.
我周一周三周五都有两小时的午休
I have a two-hour lunch Monday, Wednesday, and Friday.
夏天也不用工作
And summers off.
我要开始拿低薪了
I'm beginning to get the low pay.
这是刚刚发来的
This just in.
胡娇说 如果杰马库斯和雷蒙德都来 他就不来了
Pepper says he's not coming if both J'marcus and Raymond are here.
我要是想在这么小的地方经受这么大的压力
"If I wanted this much tension in a space that small,
我还不如去我妈那里
I'd go up to my mother's room."
这太刻薄了
That's not nice.
我们不能再来一个糟糕的派对了
We can't afford to have another bad party.
你现在就得打给雷蒙德取消邀请
You have to call Raymond right now and un-invite him.
我不敢相信你和胡娇
I-I can't believe you and Pepper
居然对人毫无同情心
aren't being more compassionate about this.
雷蒙德也是人啊
Raymond is a human being.
为什么不能邀请玛吉库斯和罗兰德他们俩
What is the problem with inviting Majarcus and Roland?
他们分手了
They had a horrible breakup.
就在几个月前
Months ago.
歌洛莉亚 你说呢
Gloria, what do you think?
在作出判决之前 我需要更多信息
I think I need to know more before I adjudicate.
判决
Adjudicate?
在天空晴朗 驴子还有劲的时候
When the skies were clear and the donkey was very strong,
我们会看《洛杉矶法律》
we would watch "L.A. Law".
那是模型屋
That is the mockup room.
大伙好啊
Hey, guys.
继续做模型[嘲笑]
Keep up the mocking.
保持幽默总是有必要的
It's important to keep it fun.
看看 设计团队正在开会
Look at that. The design team's having a meeting.
你说我们要不要进去
What do you say we go in there
说几句"干得好"之类的
and give them a couple "Attaboys", huh?
不了 他们看上去很忙
No. No, they look really busy.
别说笑了
Don't be silly.
每个人都想跟老板面对面接触
Everybody wants face time with the boss.
老妈 你还好吗
Mom, are you okay?
艾丽克斯 我没事
Alex, I'm fine.
-我的天 -怎么了
- Oh, my God. - What?
你的瞳孔就跟五分硬币一样大
Your pupil is the size of a nickel.
感觉像是半个你正在咆哮
It looks like half of you went to a rave.
克莱尔 我们有个库存问题
Claire, we have a storage problem.
如果是带镜子的门的事 我应该已经解决了
If it's those mirrored doors, I think I solved that one.
不是 有个白痴给赫姆订了一个冰淇淋蛋糕
No, some idiot ordered Herm an ice cream cake.
你们这么叫人白痴不好
I don't think that name-calling--
等等 这跟库存有什么关系
wait, how is that a storage problem?
冰箱里根本放不下那玩意儿
The damn thing won't fit in the freezer.
融化得跟什么似的
It's melting like a son of a bitch.
行 那就找一间最小的房间
Well, then, um, find the smallest room we've got
把冷气开到最大
and crank the A/C full blast, hmm?
-好建议 -谢谢你
- That's a great idea. - Thank you.
或许我们还能把杂物间的温度调高点
Maybe later, we could turn the heat up in the broom closet,
好烤些玛芬蛋糕吃
bake muffins.
完全悲剧
Complete disaster.
我有话要说
I'm gonna say something.
你们这么说也太荒唐了吧
You people are being ridiculous.
不就是个该死的薄荷蛋糕吗
It's a freaking mint chip cake.
薄荷味的吗
Mint chip?
是的 薄荷味
Yeah, mint chip.
你们会喜欢的
You're gonna love it.
就算它融了一点 那又如何
And if it's melting, so what?
我们把派对提前就是了
We move the party up a little.
干脆 你们叫所有人
In fact, why don't you tell everybody
在十分钟内布置好一切
to be in the mill in 10 minutes.
但是杰赶不过来
But Jay's not here.
对呀 谁来给赫姆致告别词呢
Yeah, who will give Herm's farewell speech?
我啊
I will.
我会给他一个此生最棒的告别词
Give him the best farewell speech Herm has ever heard.
老妈 你确定你要上吗
Mom, are you sure you're up for this?
就是 你看起来晕乎乎的
Yeah, you look a little loopy.
你们别担心 我能搞定
You know what? I'll be fine.
不过我首先得搞清楚赫姆是哪一位
Just as soon as I figure out who Herm is.
继续坚持 各位男士
Keep it up, gentlemen.
老爸 你还记得那次你被人敲竹杠吗
Hey, dad, remember that time you were getting ripped off?
你怎么还念念不忘
You're still on this.
我拍了一张那人的照片发给老妈了
I took a picture of the guy and sent it to mom.
她发誓说从没见过那个人
She swears she's never seen him before in her life.
对于她在酒吧遇到过的所有人
Your mom could say that
你妈都能说她不认识
about anyone she met at a party with an open bar.
有人又需要受点人生教育啦
Sounds like someone could use another teachable moment.
-不用了 老爸 -大家快过来抱团
- I'm good, Dad. - Men, gather 'round.
人生教 我了个
Teachable mo-- mother of...
卢克还是固执地认为我被骗了
Luke here still thinks I got ripped off,
但是如果那人真是骗子
but if that guy wasn't legit,
他又怎么知道卢克是我儿子呢
how did he know that Luke was my son?
因为我管你叫老爸
Because I called you Dad.
但是他怎么知道你以前很小呢
But how did he know that you used to be small?
我发现这里有点问题了
I get the problem with that one.
菲尔 别被他的嘲讽扰乱自己
Phil, don't give in to his hipster cynicism.
我很敬佩你这么天真地信任别人
I admire your childlike faith in people.
还有卢克 你回答我这个问题
And, Luke, answer me this.
如果这人真是个骗子
If this guy is such a con man,
他又是怎么知道你爸是"房地产先生"的
how did he know your dad was Mr. Real Estate?
棒呆
Boom!
快来人拿个麦克风给这孩子扔扔
Someone give this kid a mic to drop.
你还真问住我了
You got me.
我现在脑子都还晕乎乎的
I'm actually feeling a little dizzy because of that.
我的整个三观都被震撼了
My whole world view has been rocked.
在晕倒之前 我得赶紧坐下
I'm just gonna sit down before I pass out.
坐在鸽子粪上还装得这么拽
Pretty smug for a guy sitting on pigeon droppings.
那我也值了
Totally worth it.
当时我站在门外觉得很难过
I was standing outside feeling sorry for myself.
*孤单小豹拉里*
*Larry the lonely leopard*
*身上斑点去不掉*
*Couldn't change his spots*
*但是只要真心微笑*
*But once he put his smile on*
*好朋友们全围绕*
*Look at all the friends he's got*
然后我意识到自己就是那只孤单小豹拉里
Then I realized I was Larry the lonely leopard.
我只需要重露笑容就好了
I just needed to put my smile on.
那首歌真是穿透灵魂
That song works on so many levels.
大家好 我是乔的爸爸
Hi, gang. I'm Joe's Dad.
有谁想听故事吗
Anybody want to hear a story?
-这是个好提议 杰 -那好
- That's a great idea, Jay! - Okay.
这个故事叫《小小小屋子》
This one's called "The teeny tiny house".
在一座很小很小的镇上
"In a teeny tiny town...
一个很小很小的街区里
"On a teeny tiny block,"
有一座很小很小的房子 里面有
"Stood a teeny tiny house with a teeny tiny --"
你好老
You're old.
你见过我妻子吗 大耳仔
You seen my wife, Big Ears?
那之后 大耳仔的家长和我
After that, Big Ears' parents and I
不得不在情感桌上坐下来谈话
had to spend a little time at the feelings table.
我看看是不是搞清楚这事了
Let me see if I'm understanding this.
总的说来 你们认识雷达的时间久些
So, you have known Radar longer,
但杰玛玛为人更风趣
but Jemima is the fun one.
是的 为你越来越接近人家真正的名字点个赞
Yes, and kudos for really zeroing in on those names.
拜托 雷蒙更有趣一点好吗
Come on. Raymond's fun.
说一件他有趣的事来听听
Name one fun thing he does.
还一件 太多件了好吗
One -- so many things.
好吧 听着 他干过这事
Okay, this, he does this thing
模仿他父母的答录机
where he imitates his parents' answering machine.
真的超搞笑 每次模仿都搞笑死了
It's hilarious. It kills every time.
-那是杰马库斯好吗 -呵呵了
- And it's J'marcus. - Damn it.
米奇尔 为什么这个雷蒙德对你来说这么重要
Mitchell, why is this Raymond so important to you?
到底有什么事是不能告诉我们的
What is it that you're not telling us?
没什么
Nothing.
难道你不是对他动心了吗
Isn't it true that you have feelings for him?
我没有
No.
承认吧 你就是喜欢他
Admit it. You have a crush on him.
我没有
I don't.
你爱他 你想和他在一起
You love him. You want to be with him.
而且除非卡梅隆退出了 你才会死心
And you won't stop until Cameron is out of the picture.
好了 好了 你疯了
Okay, okay, you're -- you're crazy.
-那到底为什么 -因为
- Then why? - Be--
因为我就是雷蒙德
Because I am Raymond.
什么
What?
是的 如果我们分手了
Yeah, if -- if we ever broke up,
我们所有的朋友都会站在你那边
all of our friends would pick you,
我会被抛弃的
and I'd be the one who's left behind.
亲爱的 不是这样的
Honey, that's not true.
我会逼他们请你参加各种圈内活动的
I would make them invite you to stuff.
他在说谎 看他玩自己头发就知道
He's lying. I can tell from the way he's playing with his hair.
不 我觉得他说的是真的
No, I-I think you really got to it.
-快坦白 -好吧 是小卡
- Say it. Okay, fine. Cam!
是小卡好了吧 我担心的是小卡
Cam's the one, all right? Cam's the one I'm worried about.
他才是那个会被抛弃的人
He's the one who's gonna be left behind.
我的追问结束了
I rest my case.
可是我还没问完
Well, I don't rest mine.
为什么你觉得我会被抛弃
Why do you think I'm the one that's gonna be left behind?
我可是"舞会女神"[备受瞩目]好吗
I'm the belle of the ball.
就是这样 这种话
Right there -- that's the type of thing
你应该让别人去说
you should let other people say.
而且还要你是女生
About a woman.
没人会听你的政治呼声
Nobody really cares about your political rants.
朋友们才不想听科赫兄弟[两个富老头]的事呢
Our friends don't want to hear about the Koch Brothers.
除非你说的是一群帅基佬
Unless you're talking about a couple of hot guys
在夜店里的卫生间共浴
in a bathroom at a nightclub.
小卡 你还真是口无遮拦
Cam, you have no filter.
不管想到什么粗俗的事情你都照样说出来
You say whatever rude thing you're thinking,
这样会把别人惹不高兴[费泽斯]
and that ruffles feathers.
费泽斯有严重的口臭
Feathers has terrible breath,
而我是唯一一个坦诚告诉他的人
and I was the only one with the decency to tell him.
好 行了 你们俩都给我坐下
Okay, that's it. Both of you sit down.
我做好决定了
I have reached my decision.
雷蒙德可以来参加派对
Raymond is coming to the party.
这会是个明智的先例
It's a smart precedent to set,
因为据我今天听到的
because after what I heard here today,
我觉得你们两个
I think there is a big chance
以后很有可能都会被大家遗弃
that both of you are going to be left out.
你又没宣誓 非得要说真话吗
You know you're not under oath, right?
这不是他嘛
There he is.
好久没见了 运动服先生
How long's it been, Mr. Sport Coat?
终极的教育时刻到来了
And there it was. The ultimate teachable moment.
我猜答案是什么也没有
I guess the answer is nothing.
没什么能让我们跟动物有所区别
Nothing separates us from animals.
成熟点吧 曼尼 人类基本都很糟
Grow up, Manny. Human beings are basically terrible.
你们搞什么鬼
What the hell?
他来了 满口废话先生
There he is! Mr. Full-of-Garbage.
你们在干什么
What are you doing?
报仇 你利用我的善良 假装认识我
Payback for turning a bunch of innocent kids into cynics
就是你这种人让孩子们不再相信他人
by preying on my good nature and pretending you know me!
菲尔 我是蒙蒂·雷蒙医生
Phil -- Dr. Monty Lemon.
是我接生卢克的
I delivered Luke.
蒙蒂·雷蒙医生比你瘦 头发比你多
Dr. Monty Lemon was thinner, had more hair,
而且他比你年轻十五岁
and was a good 15 years younger than you -- oh.
对哦 我婴儿时的照片上有你
Yeah. You're in my baby photos.
谁想要蛋糕 拿杯子过来
Anybody wants cake, grab a cup.
给我来点
I'll have some.
是薄荷味的
It's mint chip.
成了
Did it.
拿到了赫姆的个人档案 还写了超赞的演讲稿
I got Herm's personnel file, and I wrote a kickass speech.
你的眼睛变成蓝黑色了
Your eye is turning black and blue.
还有你的手是怎么了
Yeah, and -- and what happened to your hand?
没什么
Nothing.
我打开档案柜的时候划破了手指
I just gashed it trying to get into the filing cabinet.
只不过缝了一两针 没什么大不了的
Nothing a stitch or two at urgent care can't fix.
"老板" 我们真要这样做吗
"Boss", are we gonna do this?
是的
Oh, we're doing this.
我知道今天发生了很多事
I know it's been a tricky day,
但我很高兴你们俩能在此见证这一切
but I am so glad the two of you are here to see this.
好了 各位 请都过来
Okay, everyone, gather 'round.
都过来
Just bring it in.
请大家把注意力都集中到我这
Let me get your attention here.
老妈 老妈
Mom! Mom!
可恶的冰淇淋蛋糕
Stupid ice cream cake.
我没事 天哪
I'm okay. Ooh. Oh, God.
妈妈 别动
Mom, stay down.
不 我得起来
No. I need this.
我知道你觉得要给我们留下好印象 但真的不用
I know you think you need to impress us, but you don't.
从小到大 你一直都感动着我们
You've impressed us our whole lives.
尤其是今天
And especially today.
除了你 没人能忍受这种惩罚
Nobody but you could put up with this much punishment
还继续装下去的
and keep going.
这对我意义重大
It means so much.
真的 但我还有工作要做
It really does, but I've got a job to do.
我要做完它
And I'm gonna do it.
赫姆对很多人来说意义非凡
Herm is so many things to so many people.
在他三个儿子心里 他是榜样
To his three sons, he is a role model.
对他妻子德洛丽丝来说 他是个忠诚的丈夫
To his wife, Dolores, he is a devoted husband.
对于他的六只营救犬来说 他...
And to his six rescue beagles, he...
-弄错赫姆了 -什么
- Wrong Herm. - What?
你说的是赫姆·安德森
You're talking about Herm Anderson.
今天退休的人是赫姆·科沃斯基
Herm Kowalski is the one who's retiring today.
有两个叫赫姆的吗
There are two Herms?
-有三个 -好吧 我放弃
- Three. - Okay, I'm out.
杰
Jay?
在这喝酒呢
In here with the booze.
你怎么样
How are you?
挺好的 怎么了
Fine. Why?
学校来电话了
The school called,
他们说有个坏孩子取笑了你
and they said that a mean boy made fun of you.
他可能会听到我们的谈话
He can probably hear us from here.
那孩子的耳朵比斯黛拉的还大
Kid had ears bigger than Stella's.
除了这些呢 感觉如何
Other than that, how was it?
就像我玩那个滑滑管一样 不合适
Like me in the tube slide -- not a good fit.
这事不适合我
Just not my thing.
别再跟我说那些增进感情的说辞了
And don't give me that business about bonding,
因为乔根本不知道我在那
because Joe didn't even know I was there.
不知是否能让你好受点
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
陪审员的事被拒绝了
I got rejected from jury duty,
所以你再也不用去学校了
so you don't have to go to school anymore.
妈妈 妈妈
Mommy! Mommy!
今天在学校怎么样
How was your school day?
最棒的一天 因为爸爸去了
Best day ever 'cause Daddy was there.
真的吗
Really?
你喜欢爸爸陪你上学吗
Did you like Daddy being in school?
他做好吃的 还读了书
He made snacks, he read books,
而且现在我管汤米叫大耳朵
and now I call Tommy "Big Ears."
很高兴你喜欢
I'm glad that stuck.
太好了
That's so nice.
爸爸 你明天还去吗
Daddy, can you come back tomorrow?
你真的希望我明天还去吗
Do you really want me to come back tomorrow?
是的
Yeah.
谁又能想到呢
What do you know?
我大受欢迎
I'm a hit.
有人吗
Anyone there?
帮个忙好吗
Little help?
谁
Hello?
汤米
Tommy?
Tommy.
我被卡在这里了
I'm kind of stuck here.
你能去找个大人来吗
Could you go get a grown-up?
抱歉 听不见你说话
Sorry. Can't hear you.
真的吗
Really?
耳朵那么大都听不到吗
With those ears?
对不起 我不该取笑你
I'm sorry, that was uncalled for.
你想要什么
What do you want?
钱吗 我有钱
Money? I got money.
拿去 信用卡随便刷
Go ahead, use the credit card.
你肯定没我老婆能花钱
You spend less than my wife.